<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Anmol Bhullar</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2017-06-13T18:30:37-04:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Anmol Bhullar</name>
   <email>anmol.bhullar@mail.utoronto.ca</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>How the set of orthogonal matrices form a (smooth) manifold.</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/06/13/ortho-manifold/"/>
   <updated>2017-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/06/13/ortho-manifold</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Preface: This article is the beginning of a series of articles about 
random parts about math that I find really cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we get started, it is always good to give some definitions so
as to avoid any confusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Not finished]&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Analysis II Notes</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/03/13/mat257-notes/"/>
   <updated>2017-03-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/03/13/mat257-notes</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;These notes are from a course called &lt;em&gt;MAT257: Analysis II&lt;/em&gt;. It is the more theoretical version of MAT237. The notes are found from
Dr. Dror Bar-Natan’s website &lt;a href=&quot;http://drorbn.net/index.php?title=1617-257&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. The notes posted here are all of them compiled into
a single document as well as having been typeset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The notes can be downloaded from my Github &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/anmolBhullar/anmolbhullar.github.io/tree/master/notes&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Not finished]&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Advanced Calculus Problem Sets</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/03/12/advanced-calc-psets/"/>
   <updated>2017-03-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/03/12/advanced-calc-psets</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;These problem sets are from a course I am taking called &lt;em&gt;MAT237: Advanced Calculus&lt;/em&gt;, it is a year long course on second year
calculus, we cover all the topics on multi-variable differentiation/integration as well as covering topology in R^n to
supplement the theory behind those topics. Later in the course, it gets quite geometric heavy as calculus naturally tends to get
more differential geometry if one to continue in it. The questions were given from &lt;a href=&quot;http://utmat237.com&quot;&gt;our class website&lt;/a&gt;.
I am posting my solutions for these problem sets below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They can be downloaded from my Github &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/anmolBhullar/anmolbhullar.github.io/tree/master/solutions/mat237&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[not finished]&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Notes for Introduction to Analysis</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/02/24/intr-to-analysis/"/>
   <updated>2017-02-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/02/24/intr-to-analysis</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The first order of business is to upload my notes for a course I’m taking called Introduction to Analysis. It covers all of the basic topics a student might need to know before they can tackle on a Real Analysis course. I will also be uploading solutions to the problems in the textbook we are using for this course which is called &lt;em&gt;Real Analysis and Foundations by Steven G. Krantz (4th Ed.)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The notes are embedded below or can be downloaded &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/anmolbhullar/anmolbhullar.github.io/tree/master/notes&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B_F-4YnSC7qdUlBGbWZFZDM2bW8/preview&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500em&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solutions of the textbook problems will start from section 4.3 which is on compactness on the real line. They can be downloaded &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/anmolbhullar/anmolbhullar.github.io/tree/master/solutions/krantz&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[not finished]&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My plans for this website</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/02/23/introducing-me/"/>
   <updated>2017-02-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/02/23/introducing-me</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my website!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the past year, I’ve been reading a fair bit of math textbooks of which I’ve made plenty of notes from and have written down solutions of problems from some of their chapters. I hope to upload these
onto this site for more organized web keeping and so that anyone in the world can access them. I hope to update this website at the most biweekly with either LaTeX’d notes or LaTeX’d solutions to
problems. I will probably upload notes to some of my courses but they will often be incomplete - especially the ones of courses I have already completed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still not sure what format I want to be uploading notes/solutions in. Currently, I have set up this website with Github Pages using Jekyll because it was a quick way of just getting my website online.
This is a problem because Github Pages are meant to be for static pages only. While I don’t plan on doing anything crazy with this website it would be nice later down the road to not have such a limitation.
Currently, I’m thinking of embedding the PDF notes/solutions using this &lt;a href=&quot;http://jamesonzimmer.com/simple-pdf-embed-for-jekyll/&quot;&gt;solution&lt;/a&gt; and giving them the option to download if they please.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/anmolbhullar/anmolbhullar.github.io&quot;&gt;Github repository&lt;/a&gt; for downloads of the pdfs, any typo reports or even feature requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
